{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Air Quality Testing Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","__cache./api/resource/task/60840/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":60840,"taskName":"Indoor Air Quality Testing","taskDescription":"Test Indoor Air Quality","xmTaskDescriptor":"Air Quality Testing Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":136,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"indoor air quality testing, air quality, testing, pollution, air pollutants, indoors, home","textMessagingName":"Indoor Air Quality Testing","rolloverLongDesc":"Allergens, mold, bacteria and dust can hide in your home's air ducts. This air circulates throughout your home when your furnace or air conditioner runs and can be unhealthy to breathe. Professionals will test the air and report back particle levels and can recommend remediation.","rolloverShortDesc":"Testing levels of allergens, mold and toxic substances in your homes air","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local companies to test indoor air quality. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened indoor air quality testing companies in your area.","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Indoor Air Quality Testing Companies","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":78,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Indoor Air Quality Testing Companies","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Indoor Air Quality Testing","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Air Quality Testing Project","urlName":"Indoor-Air-Quality-Testing","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Indoor Air Quality Testing Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"indoor air quality testing, air quality, testing, pollution, air pollutants, indoors, home","emcCategoryOid":-12072,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":6500,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/60840/":{"taskOID":60840,"originalTaskOID":60840,"setID":6500,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500720,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for test","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you want to test the homes air quality?","shortQuestionText":"Reason for test","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2378,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Family member(s) suffer cold, allergy, or asthma symptoms","answerDisplayText":"Family member(s) suffer cold, allergy, or asthma symptoms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5550,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"See evidence of dampness or other water intrusion in home","answerDisplayText":"See evidence of dampness or other water intrusion in home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4332,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Odor elimination","answerDisplayText":"Odor elimination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5180,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Renovation/remodel","answerDisplayText":"Renovation/remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200940,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Flood or fire damage restoration","answerDisplayText":"Flood or fire damage restoration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1206,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Buying pre-owned home","answerDisplayText":"Buying pre-owned home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3391,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Just want to have home checked","answerDisplayText":"Just want to have home checked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500720,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for test","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you want to test the homes air quality?","shortQuestionText":"Reason for test","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2378,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Family member(s) suffer cold, allergy, or asthma symptoms","answerDisplayText":"Family member(s) suffer cold, allergy, or asthma symptoms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5550,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"See evidence of dampness or other water intrusion in home","answerDisplayText":"See evidence of dampness or other water intrusion in home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4332,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Odor elimination","answerDisplayText":"Odor elimination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5180,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Renovation/remodel","answerDisplayText":"Renovation/remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200940,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Flood or fire damage restoration","answerDisplayText":"Flood or fire damage restoration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1206,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Buying pre-owned home","answerDisplayText":"Buying pre-owned home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3391,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Just want to have home checked","answerDisplayText":"Just want to have home checked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2378,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Family member(s) suffer cold, allergy, or asthma symptoms","answerDisplayText":"Family member(s) suffer cold, allergy, or asthma symptoms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5550,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"See evidence of dampness or other water intrusion in home","answerDisplayText":"See evidence of dampness or other water intrusion in home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4332,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Odor elimination","answerDisplayText":"Odor elimination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5180,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Renovation/remodel","answerDisplayText":"Renovation/remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200940,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Flood or fire damage restoration","answerDisplayText":"Flood or fire damage restoration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1206,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Buying pre-owned home","answerDisplayText":"Buying pre-owned home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3391,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Just want to have home checked","answerDisplayText":"Just want to have home checked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}